{"data":[{"question":"___ your clothes right away. We're going to be late.","a":"Wearing","b":"Wear","c":"Putting on","d":"Put on","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Put on: to put a piece of clothing on your body \n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Go on ___ the other exercises after you have finished this one.","a":"doing","b":"to do","c":"to be doing","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Go on + Verb_ing: Continue with something you are doing\n- Go on + To Verb: To do other thing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The terrible noise from that room simply ___ me mad.","a":"caused","b":"put","c":"turned","d":"drove","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Drive somebody crazy\/nuts\/mad\/insane (=make someone feel very annoyed)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Her parents died and ___ her a lot of fortune.","a":"left","b":"gave","c":"offered","d":"sent","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Leave (when sbd die): to arrange for someone to receive your money, property, etc after you die","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"___ this essay and tell me what you think of it.","a":"Look on","b":"Look through","c":"Look up","d":"Look into","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Look through= go through:  to look for something among a pile of papers, in a drawer, in someone's pockets etc","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"I asked the director to ___ me a few hours so that we could go over all the problems.","a":"save","b":"spend","c":"share","d":"spare","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Spare: to make something such as time, money, or workers available for someone, especially when this is difficult for you to do","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"It is well known that Thomas Edison ___ the electric lamp.","a":"discovered","b":"invented","c":"developed","d":"found","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Invent: to make, design, or think of a new type of thing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Cheap gasoline of poor quality ___ a lot of smoke.","a":"gives in","b":"gives up","c":"gives off","d":"gives away","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Give off: to produce a smell, light, heat, a sound","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Sandy and Vincent ___ friends since they met in Bangkok.","a":"have become","b":"have made","c":"have turned","d":"have been","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be friends (with somebody): to be someone's friend \n- Make friends: to become friendly with people","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The sports meet will be ___ till next Saturday because of the bad weather.","a":"put away","b":"put off","c":"put down","d":"put up","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Put off (=delay): to delay doing something or to arrange to do something at a later time or date, especially because there is a problem or you do not want to do it now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}